The Scariest House You Have Ever Seen!
Home Alone: The Holiday Heist is a comedy, family, tv
movie film directed by Peter Hewitt.
10-year-old Finn is terrified to learn his family is relocating from sunny
California to Maine in the scariest house he has ever seen!
Convinced that his new house is haunted, Finn sets up a series of
elaborate traps to catch the “ghost” in action.
Left home alone with his sister while their parents are stranded across town, Finn’s traps
catch a new target – a group of thieves who have targeted Finn’s house.
Finn Baxter, played by Christian Martyn.
Alexis Baxter, played by Jodelle Ferland.
Sinclair, played by Malcolm McDowell.
Jessica, played by Debi Mazar.
Mr. Hughes, played by Eddie Steeples.
Curtis Baxter, played by Doug Murray.
Home Alone: The Holiday Heist is a 2012 American Christmas
comedy television film directed by Peter Hewitt.
A standalone sequel to Home Alone 4 (2002), it is the fifth
installment in the Home Alone franchise.
It stars Christian Martyn, Jodelle Ferland, Malcolm
McDowell, Debi Mazar, and Eddie Steeples.
The film was produced by Fox Television Studios and premiered on ABC Family on November 25, 2012,
during the network's annual Countdown to 25 Days of Christmas programming block.
It is the second film after Home Alone 3 not to focus on the McCallister family.
The tone is lighthearted.